<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<page title="Kasije CMS" description="Kasije lightweight cms">
    <meta>
        <author>Touwolf Technologies</author>
        <description>Kasije lightweight cms</description>
    </meta>
    <section id="home" title="Home" banner="true">
        <header>
            Kasije lightweight cms, evolve the productivity.
            Our product is not this website, but the framework that enables you to access this content.
            (This page is loading on Kasije, of course ;)
        </header>
        <tip title="It is a lightweight CMS, ultra productive and extendible">
            <line duration="300" delay="100">
                Develop and host multiple websites has never been easier.
            </line>
            <link duration="300" delay="200" text="Get Started">/tutorial</link>
        </tip>
    </section>
    <section id="features" title="Features">
        <header title="What we offer">
            If you want to propose new features, please contact us.
        </header>
        <feature title="Web sites" faIcon="fa-rocket">
            <description>
                Efficiently develop multiple web sites from a single location with shared resources and resources.
                Define the content of text files in various formats (XML, JSON, YAML, etc.) and update it at any time.
                Themes can be edited in multiple templating engines (freemarker, velocity, etc.).
            </description>
        </feature>
        <feature title="Preprocessing and compression of static resources" faIcon="fa-html5">
            <description>
                Static resources that require preprocessing (Sass, typescript, CoffeeScript, etc) are processed without
                you needing to intervene, all you need is to include as it and Kasije processes it appropriately by its extension.
                Also the resources that support compression (JS and CSS) are compressed by the system and cached until they
                return to be modified. (All this features are used on this site you are reading ;)
            </description>
        </feature>
        <feature title="Separation of content and presentation" faIcon="fa-gears">
            <description>
                It is a good design philosophy that we made concrete. You will preserve the semantics of the content,
                your content will be a piece of structured information. And also you will keep all aesthetic details away
                from this structured information. Good structured information remains readable always. Your site content will
                also look more adequate to all members in your team. Everybody benefit from the separation: the content
                supplier does not have to be a good designer and vice versa.
            </description>
        </feature>
        <feature title="Easy virtual hosting" faIcon="fa-desktop">
            <description>
                Virtual Host refers to running multiples web sites on a single physical server, wich is not apparent to the end
                user. With Kasije there is no need of complicated configurations or server restarts, simply add content in the
                folder with the name of the virtual domain and the virtual host is ready (as we have done this website).
            </description>
        </feature>
        <feature title="Extendable by plugins" faIcon="fa-puzzle-piece">
            <description>
                The CMS supports the implementation of plugins to extend its core, also to provide more options for working
                with templates (engines alternatives to freemarker or velocity), formats for content editing (alternatives to
                XML or Json); preprocessing resources, among others.
            </description>
        </feature>
        <feature title="Command line interface" faIcon="fa-terminal">
            <description>
                Kasije has multiple command line tools integrated to facilitate the work on the server, as is a Java based system
                this works in all platforms and allow you to create new sites, configure, monitor their execution; among other useful
                options of operation and control systems.
            </description>
        </feature>
    </section>
</page>
