<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<page title="Kasije CMS" description="Kasije lightweight cms">
    <meta>
        <author>Touwolf Technologies</author>
        <description>Kasije lightweight cms</description>
    </meta>
    <section id="home" title="Home" banner="true">
        <header>
            Kasije lightweight cms, evolve the productivity.
            Our product is not this website, but the framework that enables you to access this content.
            (This page is loading on Kasije, of course ;)
        </header>
        <tip title="It is a lightweight CMS, ultra productive and extendible">
            <line duration="300" delay="100">
                Develop and host multiple websites has never been easier.
            </line>
            <link duration="300" delay="200" text="Get Started">/tutorial</link>
        </tip>
    </section>
    <section id="features" title="Features">
        <header title="What we offer">
            If you want to propose new features, please contact us.
        </header>
        <feature title="Websites" faIcon="fa-rocket">
            <description>
                Efficiently develop multiple websites from a single location with shared resources and templates.
                Define the content of text files in various formats (XML, JSON, YAML, etc.) and update it at any time.
                Themes can be edited in multiple templating engines (freemarker, velocity, etc.).
            </description>
        </feature>
        <feature title="Preprocessing and compression of static resources" faIcon="fa-html5">
            <description>
                Static resources that require preprocessing (Sass, typescript, CoffeeScript, etc) are processed without
                your intervention, all you need to do is include them as they are, and Kasije will process them appropriately by their extension.
                Also the resources that support compression (JS and CSS) are compressed by the system and cached until they
                return to be modified. (All this features are used on this site you are reading ;)
            </description>
        </feature>
        <feature title="Separation of content and presentation" faIcon="fa-gears">
            <description>
                It is a good design philosophy that we made concrete. You will preserve the semantics of the content,
                your content will be a piece of structured information. With features such as Kasije theme sharing, you can define
                and share themes among your sites and still keep all aesthetic details separated
                from the subject, allowing your information schema to be always readable. Everybody benefits from the separation: the content
                supplier does not have to be a good designer and vice versa.
            </description>
        </feature>
        <feature title="Easy virtual hosting" faIcon="fa-desktop">
            <description>
                Virtual Host refers to running multiples websites on a single physical server, which is not apparent to the end
                user. Kasije leaves no room for complicated configurations or server restarts, simply add content in the
                folder with the name of the virtual domain and the virtual host will be ready (as we have done with this website).
            </description>
        </feature>
        <feature title="Extensible by plugins" faIcon="fa-puzzle-piece">
            <description>
                The CMS supports the implementation of plugins to extend its core features, provide more options for working
                with templates (engines alternatives to freemarker or velocity), support formats for content editing (alternatives to
                XML or Json) and support other resource kinds preprocessing.
            </description>
        </feature>
        <feature title="Command line interface" faIcon="fa-terminal">
            <description>
                Kasije has multiple command line tools integrated to facilitate the work on the server, its Java based nature
                makes it run on most platforms and allow you to create new sites, configure and monitor them in the most natural
                way.
            </description>
        </feature>
    </section>
</page>
